<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>MARKETING</title>
    <description>In today’s digital age, mobile devices have become an extension of ourselves. Discover the tips and techniques marketers need to prosper in the mobile era.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <link>https://www.mirabelsmarketingmanager.com/blog/</link>
    <guid>https://www.mirabelsmarketingmanager.com/blog/</guid>

    <!-- Author and dc:creator for the channel -->
    <author>Victoria Ang</author>
    <dc:creator>Victoria Ang</dc:creator>

    <!-- An example item with an image in the description -->
    <item>
      <title>BAD SENDER REPUTATION? HERE'S HOW TO CHECK YOURS AND ULTIMATELY FIX IT</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.mirabelsmarketingmanager.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/5f63abde5442625d8ed8abbc_shutterstock_1570126813-2.jpg" alt="Image Alt Text" /><br />Email is a strong marketing strategy to directly reach your digital audience and keep them informed on product updates, service announcements, special offers, and more.
However, email marketing may prove ineffective if not successfully delivered to inboxes. One key factor that affects email deliverability is your sender reputation. Sender reputation goes by a few common names: Email sender reputation, sender score, domain reputation.
Yet, no matter what you call it, email sender reputation describes how Internet Service Providers (ISPs) like Google, Microsoft, and Yahoo judge your outgoing email. More specific inbox providers include Gmail, Outlook, Yahoo, and Hotmail.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.mirabelsmarketingmanager.com/blog/how-do-you-check-your-sender-reputation-and-how-can-you-fix-a-bad-one/</link>
      <guid>https://www.mirabelsmarketingmanager.com/blog/how-do-you-check-your-sender-reputation-and-how-can-you-fix-a-bad-one/</guid>

      <!-- Author and dc:creator for the item -->
      <author>Victoria Ang</author>
      <dc:creator>Victoria Ang</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHY VALID EMAIL ADDRESSES ARE ESSENTIAL … AND INVALID ONES CAN BE DANGEROUS!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.mirabelsmarketingmanager.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/5f63abde5442625d8ed8abbc_shutterstock_1570126813-2.jpg" alt="Image Alt Text" /><br />In order to create a successful email marketing campaign, you first need a healthy email list full of valid email addresses. It’s important that your message is delivered to legitimate inboxes in order to increase engagement rate, decrease spam complaints and unsubscribes, and more.
A healthy email list helps you avoid any long-term consequences affecting your sender reputation, such as getting blacklisted by inbox providers or falling into phishing scams or honeypot traps. SendInBlue reminds us that a clean email list with valid contacts ensures:To ensure you know how to tell if an email address is valid (as well as how to avoid invalid email addresses), Mirabel’s Marketing Manager will discuss the difference between invalid and valid email addresses. We’ll also list email verification tools that you can use to grow a healthy email list for future marketing campaigns.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.mirabelsmarketingmanager.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/5f6b350e75555227ec430b22_shutterstock_1049177441-1.jpg</link>
      <guid>https://www.mirabelsmarketingmanager.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/5f6b350e75555227ec430b22_shutterstock_1049177441-1.jpg</guid>

      <!-- Author and dc:creator for the item -->
      <author>Victoria Ang</author>
      <dc:creator>Victoria Ang</dc:creator>
    </item>
    
  

    <!-- Add more items with images in the description as needed -->

  </channel>
</rss>
